Gen!
Yeah?
Will you take these vegetables to Old Lü?
Sure.
Dongdong
Bobo
Mang Yan
Kali
Gen
Mutou
Yunfei
Da Shuang
Service staff:
Tu Bei
Tu Yi
Hu Niu
Kucha
Tianshu
Dandan
Fenmo
Grandpa:
Huang Zhenji
Gen, Xiaohei, Xiaobai:
Shan Xin
Tanjiu, Musi, Axian:
Ding Dang
Piyu:
Tao Bao
Heishu:
Ai Suo
Sun Yujing
Sun Zhongyang
Wang Miao
Bohe
Good morning.
I'm Xiaobai, your teacher.
I'm the interpretator.
On today's lesson,
we'll learn what not to eat.
What did you draw up there?
Grandpa, don't disturb my lesson!
I'm outta here.
Peace and Quiet
Let me explain with real objects.
Which he's eating.
Please! You must listen to me!
You can't eat that.
Why?
Because if you don't listen to me, you can't be here with us.
Don't feel bad about it.
If you get hungry,
I'll give you lots of wood to eat.
So be a good boy!
I'll be!
Looks like it's easier to teach him using food.
Don't translate this.
This is convenient!
It's a shame it caused so much damage.
A shark?!
Why is there a shark here?
It's no shark.
It's quite big...
A water spirit?
Was it drawn here by the flood?
Or driven out from the village by it...
I hope it can understand me...
Stay away!
Shoot...
Now I've gone and done it.
Ancestral shrine of the Wei family
Get out of there!
Can I eat this?
Of course, you can eat this.
Xiaohei, you're back!
Have you healed enough for today?
Yeah.
You can eat it.
Wow.
How about that? I'm a good teacher.
Sure.
Thanks to Heishu!
Can I eat this?
Sure...
He keeps asking you?
I feel we'll have a problem...
Can I eat this?
This you can eat,
but you can't go on like this...
Piyu!
Did you know?
If you eat too much, you get stuck at one place.
Uh-oh.
Didn't know that...
You believed this...?
It's gone.
Seems he's just on the way.
What?!
Was this your ability now?
Like this.
Wow...
Awesome!
You can get food without getting out of bed!
Piyu's scared stiff...
I found him.
Where is he?
100 miles southwest.
Are you sure it's him?
He fits your description.
Ice type by appearance.
We'll look into it first.
Why look for him?
Laozi announced that the Sky Pearl
was taken the day after we went there.
So what?
If Diting and Xuanli were there,
who could have taken the Pearl from them?
Laozi could.
Fine. Who else could?
Diting is Laozi's man.
But Xuanli isn't.
So you think Xuanli took the Pearl?
I'm 60 percent sure.
So we must look into it.
But if it's really Xuanli,
we can't stand up against him.
Head-on attacks are not my style.
'Cause you're weak at close combat?
Silence.
The flood has finally gone!
Let's go!
Cultivate now
Cultivate later
We'll need to tear down the whole roof...
Power Struggle
It's gonna be big work...
Are you sure I can't ask Laozi for compensation?
Don't worry.
It's not that big a deal.
I can fix it easily.
My saved money...
Chirr
Chirp
Chill
Chili...
The house gets much more light now.
So should I build an open-air kitchen?
No.
I'd die of heat when the air con doesn't run.
Air con
↙
It seems it will be very hot today.
Xiaobai!
I'll do the sweeping.
You bring two watermelons from Big Ji's.
Okay.
All set.
Let's go!
Hello, Auntie Cow!
Good morning, meow!
Good afternoon, meow!
Good evening, meow, meow, meow!
Enemy detected.
We're almost there.
Got you!
Gen wants to challenge me?
I'm here for watermelons.
Welcome.
This way, please.
New guys arrived.
At last, someone to bully.
I'll sweep later...
Xiaohei, keep an eye on Piyu!
I will.
They're here.
Get them!
Are these two fine?
What you choose is perfect.
Only you guys are home?
Dad and Mom are out at the watermelon fields.
What's with these guys?
- Why didn't you say he's that strong?!
- Would you have believed it?
- I still can't!
- Yeah, sure!
- It caught up!
- This one's not so bad!
What do we do?
- Run!
- We're already running!
Gathering?
What the heck is this?
There you go.
Thanks, Big Ji!
Let's go!
Heishu, where's everyone else?
Well, well. A cat beat you?
You're useless.
Told you not to mess with us, cats!
- He's stronger than you!
- You talk like a loser!
- Then fight him!
- You don't scare me!
- And who gave you that scar on your face?
- What about yours?
- I got it when I tripped up!
- We tripped up together!
Is it him?
He looks weak.
You'll regret that.
Listen, newcomer. I am...
You're so insolent!
Brother Gray was careless.
But I will...
Boss!!
They're home.
So Xiaohei found Piyu?
Let's hurry back!
What happened here?
Dongdong
Bobo
Mang Yan
Kali
Gen
Mutou
Yunfei
Da Shuang
Service staff:
Tu Bei
Tu Yi
Hu Niu
Kucha
Dandan
Fenmo
Grandpa,
Big Ji:
Huang Zhenji
Gen,
Xiaobai,
Xiaohei,
Cow,
Lil Ji,
Hen,
Doggie:
Shan Xin
Sound engineer:
Animals:
Huang Zhenji
Cute Little Wolf (Ke'ai Xiaolang)
C Minor (C Xiaodiao)
Jin Qi
Mutou
Tutehameng
Paomu Zhongyang
Ding Dang
Youwu Yueshan
Silly Bear Da (Da Chixiong)
Gen
Little Serial Killer (Xiao Liansha)
Piyu:
Tao Bao
Heishu:
Ai Suo
Sun Yujing
Sun Zhongyang
Wang Miao
Bohe
Work is done
The flood has damaged the ancestral shrine?
Yes.
The mayor's asking for donations.
Okay.
I'll be there shortly.
The ancestral shrine?
Yes.
Everyone's home is in a mess now.
I'm afraid no one can donate.
I almost forgot about it...
What are you doing up there?
Looking if we have some money left.
It's all right.
I'll take care of it.
You?
You just tell the mayor about it.
I'll renovate the shrine.
How do you get money?
As far as I know, we've got a check.
So we can claim it?
Sure.
This would be a great help for the village.
It's nothing...
We're leaving now!
You go too...?
There's a bus to town anyway.
And I can visit Shan Xin.
Isn't it dangerous?
Don't worry.
It's weird you have clothes on.
You say it like I usually had none on.
City Park
Dongdong
Bobo
Mang Yan
Kali
Gen
Mutou
Yunfei
Da Shuang
Snotty Boiled Liver ZC
(Biti Chaogan ZC)
Dandan
Fenmo
Service staff:
Tu Bei
Tu Yi
Hu Niu
Kucha
Grandpa:
Huang Zhenji
Gen, Xiaobai, Xiaohei:
Shan Xin
He won't speak
in this episode
↘
Gatekeeper, Tu Bei:
Baomu Zhongyang
Kali:
Xiahou Luofeng
Qingqiu:
Teng Xin
Fu:
Tutehameng
Sound engineer:
Piyu:
Tao Bao
Heishu:
Ai Suo
Sun Yujing
Sun Zhongyang
Wang Miao
Bohe
Is this really the place?
It should be, according to the address...
Children!
Who are you looking for?
Good morning! We'd like to meet the manager.
Do you have an appointment?
No.
Access card?
We've got it!
Is this it?
It's from Laozi.
Where are your parents?
No good?
Children.
A paper with a scribble on is not an access card.
Maybe he pulled our legs...?
I think there's a possibility...
So what do we do now?
Just go home?
We'll have to sneak in.
Just get further from the gate.
Piyu!
We can get in from here.
But this wall's quite tall...
How do we get in?
Xiaohei can help.
Come here!
He's inside!
He's looking for a landing place.
I'll go in first.
Wait, and don't move.
We're inside!
Xiaohei, you're awesome!
It's like the forest again.
Yeah.
We'd be here if we entered at the gate.
Now we should be around here.
Our destination is here.
We don't know the scale of the map.
But we'll need to pass a hill.
It looks like it's far away...
Wait a minute! Xiaohei could teleport us there!
Now I can do it only within 5 yards...
I see...
This is strange...
Trees are bigger here than in the mountains.
They easily are several hundred years old.
They take care of them well, right?
It can't be of a natural reason.
Xiaobai, look at this!
Coming!
We're that high already?
Maybe I can see our house.
That's the visitor's office, according to the map.
Those buildings in the distance must be our destination.
There should be spirits there.
Let's go there.
Someone must find us on the way.
And what do we do then?
This is why we came, to find someone.
You're right.
We've found someone.
Are you first-time visitors?
Yes.
Who introduced you to us?
Laozi.
Do you know him?
Naturally.
That means you are Lord Xuanli.
Please call me Gen.
Excuse us for breaking in.
Don't worry about it.
Everyone enters like that.
I am Tu Bei, the secretary.
Our hall manager has been waiting for you.
Please follow me.
Hall manager?
It's the same as Laozi's place.
What do you mean by this, sir?
A tiger??
Mr. Fu.
Please don't do that.
I didn't do anything dangerous.
He can talk!
I can't believe you let a human in.
He really can talk!
Why the bloody hell?!
A Siberian tiger.
You think I'm a country bumpkin if I talk like that?!
There is no rule saying humans can't enter.
Mr. Fu, please don't make me intervene.
I loathe humans.
So cool!
This won't make me like humans!
But you wear human clothes.
Not with pleasure!
Then take them off.
Don't mess with me!
I swear I devour her!
I must apologize for Mr. Fu's behavior.
Who is he?
Mr. Fu is a spirit, one of our clients.
What is this place, actually?
Didn't Laozi tell about it?
No.
Then the hall manager will.
After all, it's his job.
What?
You say they have the Sky Pearl?
Indeed.
Are you sure?
When was the last time I was wrong?
Manager.
Lord Xuanli has arrived.
This hole is pretty deep.
What is he doing down there?
I'm Kali, the hall manager.
Welcome to our Spirit Club Hall,
Lord Xuanli.
Lord Xuanli is this person here.
Oh.
Stay with me aruite yukou ishikoro wo kette
Stay with me - let's walk on, kicking pebbles as we go
Yukisaki wa kitto kimagure demo
Our destination may be whimsical
Hana no kaori wo ryoute ni
But with the scent of flowers in both hands
kore kara deau kimi e to
I’ll carry it to the you I’ve yet to meet
Wait for me hanashi wo shiyou kata wo narabete
Wait for me — let’s talk, side by side
Hajimemashite wa gikochinaku temo
Even if our first “hello” is a little awkward
Mochiyotta hako aketara
When we open the boxes we’ve brought
Tsumekon da yume wo wakeaou
Let’s share the dreams we’ve packed inside
Mata ashita tte atarimae ni kawaseru hibi ga
The days when we can casually say “See you tomorrow”
Itoshikute hakanasugite
Are so precious and so fleeting
Omoi wa kitto kienai
Those feelings will never fade away
Sora wo nagareru kumo ni wa oitsukenai kedo
We can’t catch up to the clouds drifting across the sky
Ame ni natte hana wo tsukete kitto boku wo yonderu
But they’ll turn to rain, bloom into flowers
Kitto boku wo yonderu
And surely, they’re calling out to me